片名: 叛谍追击
布鲁塞尔 比利时
中情局总部 弗吉尼亚州
国际行动信息中心
安特卫普 比利时
7点15分了!
7:15!
针对..
..during the class action suit
比利时海岸"宁静号"沉船事故,最近做出判决
against the mother company of Serenity, the ship that sank off the Belgium coast.
遇难者家属获得赔偿..
The families seeking damages for the loss of loved ones met a roadblock.
但遇难者家属之一皮特斯拒绝了..
One of those families, The Pieters, were not..
你干嘛翻我的东西?
Why are you going through my stuff?
当我小的时候,我就知道该怎么做
When I was a kid, and that was a 100 years ago and you'll never be my age,
如果你懂得..
but, we actually..
拿成绩单给我看就没事了
got the report card and took it home to our parents so they could see it.
妈妈从来不管我的闲事
Mom never went through my stuff.
-呃,我不是你妈-没错!
-Well, I mean, I'm not mom.-Yeah, no shit!
嘿!
Hey!
我找不到我的呼吸器
I can't find my filters.
如果你是呼吸器,你会待在哪?
Well, if you were a filter, where would you be?
你在说什么呢?
I don't even know what that means.
如果我是呼吸器..
If I were a filter..
我愿意待在柜子的第二层
I would be in the cabinet, on the second shelf.
我不允许你这学期不及格
I'm not having you flunk this semester, young lady!
那里面是牛奶!?
Is that milk in it?
爸爸,牛奶里的酶会引起过敏
Dad, milk enzymes cause food allergies.
妈妈用大豆做豆浆
Mom always used soy.
你喜欢那些基因改造大豆?
You'd rather drink a genetically modified bean?
明白了
Right.
-在美国你就拿这种成绩?-不是
-Did you get these kind of grades in the States?-No.
艾米,你愿意和我一起努力吗?
Amy, if we're gonna make this work, we both have to try.
是赛迪,我走了
That's Sadie, I gotta go.
就在今晚颁奖,别忘了!
It's my awards time already tonight. Can't forget.
好了,别迟到,好吗?
Alright. Don't be late, okay?
好,然后我们讨论一下你成绩单的事
Alright, and then we'll gonna talk about this report card.
什么?
What?
你不准备亲我吗?
You're not gonna kiss me goodbye?
当然会,我刚想这么做
Sure, of course I was, I was going to.
你好,沃尔特
Bonjour, Walter.
-我给你加了两块糖-啊,谢谢,洛根先生!
-I got you two sugars this time.-Ah, thanks, Mr.Logan!
我已经仔细查看过"哈尔盖特"安全系统
I thought Halgate owned the security devices we're testing.
你过来看看
I need you to look at this.
看见数字吗?看..
You read the number? Now, look.
我查了虹膜扫描的专利文献
I checked the patent for the iris scanner
看看原始图表是否有漏洞
to see if the original schematic reveal any weaknesses.
你知道我发现了什么?
You know what I found?
-有人弄错了,我们没有那个专利-那怎么可能?
-Somebody made a mistake, we don't own the patent.-No, how can that be?
我们必须查一下其他的专利,明白吗?
We must own these devices. Check the other patents, okay?
我们走吧
Let's go.
你叫我们去测试我们的保安系统
You asked us to review our security devices for flaws, so..
不输入密码,使用破解
if you don't have the pass code and wanna smash your way in..
锁的表面有一层聚合物
our smart locks burn into a hard polymer sealant here,
非常坚固,明白妈?
that permanently secures the lock. Okay?
我们没打算破解密码
We couldn't hack the pass codes,
加密算法没问题
these algorithms were some of the most secure we've encountered.
但是,我们发现
But, we found
把以下两种混合物
that if you first inject..
注入该装置硫化物和..
it's just a mix of ordinary household bleach
漂白剂的混合物
and sulfur compound in the mechanism..
哦,对不起,德里克
Oh, see, I'm sorry, Derek.
请继续
Please, go ahead.
锁就被破解了
The lock becomes useless,
我们必须找到一种解决方案
so we have to find a solution that isn't
阻止硫化反应
compromised by ordinary household bleach.
下一步
Next.
科勒先生?
Mr.Kohler? If you please..
最后一个系统
The last system.
哈尔盖特生物扫瞄系统,H1原型
Halgate biometric scanner, model H1P,
美国和欧州联合研制
providing level 3 security to U.S. military facilities in mainland Europe.
我们试过不同的破解模式
Now, we tried a variety of attacks to break in, and..
都没有成功,除非我们..
this one was tough, but one proved successful. We have a montage..
把50个虹膜,按特定的顺序扫瞄
of 50 specific irises in a specific group pattern.
开了!一眨眼的功夫
And you're in! Just brute force.
好极了!本,像往常一样
Excellent, Ben. As always.
我们将改正这个漏洞
Let's fix these flaws quickly, and..
把报告和那个虹膜序列发给我
please send me the video along with your report.
我会让我的团队跟进
I'll make sure our people get on this also.
谢谢
Thank you.
德里克,等一下
Derek, you got a second?
嗯,好的,本
Yeah, sure, Ben.
我想警告你
I think there's something you should know.
专利还没建档
Somebody forgot to file patents on these products.
专利?你怎么知道?
Patents? How do you know?
我们查看原始专利文献
Well, we pulled the original schematics to see if we could spot any weaknesses, and..
整个美国都依赖我们的保安系统
Personnel all over the world rely on the fact that our equipment is secure,
-如果它们不可靠..-我知道,本
-and that security is compromised with somebody..-I know what it means, Ben.
-真这么严重?-我们还在观察
-How bad is it?-Well, we got people looking into it.
好吧,呃..
Okay, well..
有进展就通知我,但不要告诉别人
Keep on it, keep me informed. Keep it between us.
我想今晚就看到你的详细报告
I look forward to your full presentation report tonight.
今晚?德里克,我女儿..
Tonight? Derek, my daughter..
求求你,本
Please, Ben, please.
会议什么时候开始?
What time the next batch get in here?
早上8点!不,没问题,我会到的
8 a.m. No, that's fine, I'll be here.
-嘿,弗洛伊德!-你关门?
-Hey, Floyd!-Are you okay to lock up?
-沃尔特会关-好
-Walter's gonna do it.-Okay.
8点了!洛根先生,你该回家了
It's eight! Mr.Logan, you should go home.
哦,见鬼
Oh, shit.
嘿,洛根先生!
Hey, Mr.Logan!
-安德莱赫特赢了?-没有
-Anderlecht win?-No.
他们还是落后!
They're losing again!
-1小时后在总部由导游带领出发-好
-Courier's picking that up for head office in an hour.-Okay.
太好了,罗齐!
Well done, Rosie!
现在,一等奖!
Okay now, the first prize!
最佳照片将获得1张250欧元的支票
A check for 250 euros for best photo essay.
艾米・洛根,"我的国家"
Amy Logan, "Homeland".
-哦,嗨,洛根先生-嗨,赛迪
-Oh, hi, Mr.Logan.-Hi, Sadie.
-艾米赢了!-她赢了?
-Amy won!-She won?
是的,她赢得一等奖!
Yeah, she won first prize!
她在哪?上面?
Where is she? Is she up there?
她和朋友在一起
She's with some friends.
等等!
Wait!
艾米!
Amy!
嘿!
Hey!
嘿,我必须走了
Hey, I gotta go.
-什么?-我必须走了
-What?-I gotta go.
-回头见-回头见
-See you.-See you later.
系上安全带
Put your seat belt on.
他是谁?
Who was that?
纳比尔
Nabil.
他帮了我
He's helping me.
-嗯,帮了你什么?-"沉默"
-Yeah, helping you with what?-"Without Voices."
我的下一个照片集
It's my next photo essay.
你知道,人们到这里谋生,是因为他们在原来的国家混不下去
You know, people making life here because we screwed up whatever country they're from.
那是他们的原因,不是你的问题
Don't get caught up on other people's problems.
天,要是每个人都像你这么想那就不得了了!
Boy, what a world this would be if everyone thought like you!
-你不该在整天呆在那儿-而你答应了我就该准时到达
-And you shouldn't be hanging out there.-And you should show up when you say you will.
你有什么吃的?
Do you have anything to eat?
知道吗?
You know what?
美玲带给你一些点心
Mei Ling brought you cookies.
-我不吃甜点-我没别的了
-I thought I don't eat sweets.-It's all I've got.
我今天收到电话账单了
I got the phone bill today.
打给你祖父就花了300欧元?
300 euros of calls to your Grandfather?
有花生在里面?
Has this got peanuts in it?
我觉得不太舒服,爸爸
I don't feel so good, dad.
-你还好吧?-不太好
-You okay?-No.
-嗯?-不!
-Huh?-No!
好了,坚持住!
Okay, hold on.
8点,办公室快递
你可以见她了
You can see her.
医生说你死不了
Doc says you're gonna live.
-告诉过你我对花生过敏的-对不起
-Told you I had a peanut allergy.-I'm sorry.
我应该要确认
I should have asked.
我得去趟办公室收一个快递
We have to go to the office and pick up a delivery.
不会很久的
Won't be long.
我发现一个打棒球的好地方
Did I tell you I found a place we can watch baseball?
在根特,外国人聚居的社区
In Ghent. Expat community.
我们可以去那里逛逛
Thought we could go there, hang out. Fun.
我讨厌棒球
I hate baseball.
你妈妈和我刚认识的时候,我们总是一起去玩
When your mom and I first met, we used to go to games all the time.
是啊,要是真那么好,那你为什么离开她?
Yeah, if it was so great, then why'd you leave?
你好,沃尔特
Bonjour, Walter.
你好!
Bonjour!
沃尔特?
Walter?
爸爸?
Dad?
是这层楼吗?过来!
Are we on the right floor? Come here!
你在打给谁?
Who are you calling?
我们办公室号码在这
Our office number here.
见鬼
Shit.
什么事?
What's going on?
一定是开玩笑,来吧
Some kind of misunderstanding. Come on.
爸爸,你的房间没长翅膀
Dad, your company can't just pick up and leave.
好了,如果你是个房间,你会藏在哪?
Okay, if you were a company, where would you hide?
还没开始
Don't start.
我们去布鲁塞尔
We're going to Brussels.
什么?
What?
要去搞清楚怎么回事
An hour to get there, an hour to clear this up,
我们会回来吃午餐
we'll be back by lunch.
爸爸,我有课
Dad, I have school.
那你放假一天吧
You just got the day off.
布鲁塞尔 比利时
哈尔盖特集团,跨国公司
The Halgate group: A world-wide enterprise bringing the latest
从事海上运输,大型建筑业务
technological advances to shipping, construction and engineering.
-你好-你好
-Bonjour.-Bonjour.
-我来见德里克・科勒-请等一下
-I'm here to see Derek Kohler, please.-One moment, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
不准拍照,女士
No pictures, young lady.
对不起
Sorry.
我们电脑没这名字,先生
The database is not showing a Derek Kohler, sir.
-不可能-有没有别的名字我再试一次?
-That's impossible.-Is there another name you want me to try?
是的,请再试一次.K-O-L-H-E-R
Yes, please try again. It's K-O-L-H-E-R.
-对不起!-这很重要,拜托..
-Excuse me!-It's very important, please, just..
-我知道数据库里有-对不起!
-I know he's in the database.-Excuse me!
再试一次,好吗?
Try it again, will you?
保安!
Security!
我不知道怎么说,洛根先生
I don't know how to say this, Mr.Logan.
你没有,从来没有在我们的子公司干过
But you do not, nor have you ever worked for a subsidiary of this company.
我们根本不制造这种
We don't even make this kind
保安系统.我们也从来没有雇用过
of security systems. And we never employed a..
德里克・科勒
a Derek Kohler.
听着..
Listen to me.
一家叫作"安置方案"的纽约公司,3个月前来找我
A New York based company called "Placement Solutions" came to me three months ago,
说他们想在欧洲开一家哈尔盖特的子公司
said they wanted to open a new division of The Halgate Group in Europe,
去拓展保安系统市场
as part of their-your-private security business.
洛根先生,你现在就在欧洲哈尔盖特集团总部
Mr.Logan, you are in the European headquarters of The Halgate Group.
我们负责自己的招募事宜
We handle all our recruitment direct.
我需要你的电池
I need your battery.
我的没电了
Mine's dead.
我想给你看看我的电子邮件
I wanna show you my e-mail.
谢谢
Thank you.
有我的工作电邮,8个星期的工作
It's my business correspondence. It's eight weeks in work.
-你的工作电邮?-是的
-Your business correspondence?-That's right.
你的黑莓手机里是空的
Your BlackBerry is empty.
我们查了你的背景,洛根先生
We've run a background check on you, Mr.Logan.
看来你在安特卫普待了8个星期
Seems you've been living in Antwerp now, eight weeks,
如你所说
as you say.
但你的上一个地址却在纽约..
But your last registered address was New York,
14年前的
14 years ago.
之前,在华盛顿特区,1989年
Before that, Washington D.C. 1989.
从那时起
Since then,
没有你的其他任何记录
no records of any kind exist for you.
你为一个根本不存在的哈尔盖特子公司工作
You've been working for a Halgate subsidiary which doesn't exist.
为我们根本不生产的产品做测试
Testing products we don't make.
向一个我们从未雇用过的人报告
Reporting to an officer we have never employed.
你付给我薪水
I've received paychecks from you.
我享受你们的退休福利,医疗,汽车保险
I have received pension, medical insurance, car insurance.
洛根先生..
Mr.Logan..
如果你是我
If you were in my shoes,
听到你这样的故事
listening to your story,
你会怎么做?
what would you do?
那肯定是个错误,我的薪资帐号会证明的
There must be some sort of mistake. My salary payments, they should be listed here.
不幸的是,证据摆在这里
I'm afraid that this is all we have, this is all there is.
帐号一直都没有动过..
There is no activity in your account
自从开户以来
since you opened it.
-洛根先生!-弗洛伊德!
-Mr.Logan.-Floyd!
-很高兴见到你!-你在这干嘛?
-Am I glad to see you!-What are you doing here?
公司消失不见了!发生什么事了?
The company. Everything is gone! What's going on?
我不知道,我的电邮,银行帐号,我的记录,所有的一切都消失了
I don't know. My e-mails, bank statements, my records, everything's gone.
别出声,别突然移动
Don't make a sound. No sudden moves.
嘿,你能把我的支票..
Hey, can you cash my..
兑现吗?
check?
-你为什么这么做,弗洛伊德?-走高速
-Why are you doing this, Floyd?-Get on the autoroute.
我们去哪里?
Where are we going?
把手放在方向盘上
Hands on the wheel.
我会照你说的做
I'll do exactly as you say.
弗洛伊德,公司发生什么事了?
Floyd, what happened to the company?
告诉我,弗洛伊德
Talk to me, Floyd.
告诉我,该死的.你为什么干这种事?
Talk to me, damned. Why are you doing this?
看路!
Eyes on the road!
-别撞他-闭嘴!
-Don't hit him.-Shut up!
没事的,宝贝
It's okay, baby.
坐好
Just sit back.
艾米?
Amy?
告诉过你要系好安全带
I thought I told you to always put your your seatbelt on.
走第三个出口
Take the third exit.
你打算怎么办?
What are you gonna do?
你为谁工作?
Who are you working for?
你该照我说的做,本
You should have taken my advice, Ben.
我告诉你回家
I told you to go home.
现在他们让我来找你了,你们两个
Now they made me come looking for you. For both of you.
走这个出口
Take this exit.
就是这个出口!转弯!
Take this exit out! Take it!
没事的,艾米
It's okay, Amy.
-减速!-爸爸,减速!
-Slow down!-Dad, slow down!
减速!
Slow down!
爸爸,小心!
Dad, watch out!
爸爸!
Dad!
爸爸,方向盘!
Dad, the wheel!
爸爸!
Dad!
你为谁工作,弗洛伊德?
Who you're working for, Floyd?
我想知道答案,弗洛伊德
I want answers, Floyd.
我要是回家会怎么样?
What was waiting for me at home?
你为谁工作?你究竟为谁工作?
Who you're working for? Who you're working for?
哦,我的天!
Oh, my God!
爸爸,警察能帮我们的
Dad, the cops, they can help us.
-他们帮不了-不,他们可以的!
-They can't help us.-Yes, they can!
不,他们不行
No, they can't.
快走
Come on.
退后!
Get back!
退后
Stay back.
嘿,过来,你受伤了?我们不能..
Hey, come here, you hurt? We can't..
我们不能呆在这儿,爸爸,这是人家的屋子!
We can't be here, dad, this is someone's house!
我们不会呆很久的
We won't be here long.
拉上窗帘
Draw the curtains.
你杀了他
You killed him.
这是自卫,艾米
In self-defense, Amy.
不,爸爸,太糟糕了
No, Dad, this is messed up.
真是一团糟!
This is so messed up!
我现在需要你的帮助,好吗?
I need you to help me right now, okay?
把拇指包起来
Over the top, around the thumb.
我们去找警察,爸爸,他们可以帮我们
We could still go to the police, dad. They can help us.
我们昨晚应该待在家里面
We should've been at home last night.
这是他所希望的
He wanted us to go home.
这是什么?
What's that?
像是个储物柜钥匙
Looks like a locker key.
"AC"
"A.C."
安特卫普中心
"Antwerp Central."
你为国务院工作,你何不打电话找他们?
You used to work for The State Department. Why don't you call someone?
告诉他们什么?我的电邮被删除了
And tell them what? Someone erased my e-mails,
银行帐号,我的全部生活..
bank records, my life?
艾米!
Amy!
为什么你的同事想杀我们?
Why would someone you work with try to kill us?
艾米,听我说,我不明白发生了什么
Amy, listen to me. I don't know what's going on here.
来
Come here.
现在,对你最安全的地方
The safest place for you to be, right now,
就是待在我身边,并照我说的去做
is at my side listening to what I tell you.
好吗?
Will you do that for me?
你相信我吗?
Will you trust me?
安特卫普中心
退后
Get back.
你看见那些摄像机了?
You see those cameras up there?
别抬头
You keep your head down.
如果看不见整个轮廓,他们就无法识别
They can't identify you if they can't get a full profile.
我去储物柜那儿,在这等我
I'm going to the lockers. Wait for me here.
-拐角处是安全的-爸爸?
-Corners are safe.-Dad?
我不会让你出事的
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
-你在哪里得到的?-弗洛伊德的储物柜
-Where did you get that?-From Floyd's locker.
美玲
Mei Ling.
他们是谁?
Who are they?
我办公室同事
People I work with.
那是我
That's my picture.
这是我祖父和我在纽黑文的照片
That's a picture of Grandpa and me in New Haven.
这家伙怎么得到的?
How did this guy get this stuff?
这家伙怎么会有我4个月前的相片?
How can this guy have a picture of me from four months ago?
你怎么能这样冷静?
How can you be so calm?
因为那是我们弄明白整件事情的唯一途径
'Cause that's the only way we're gonna figure out what's going on.
让我想想,好吗?
Just let me work this out, okay?
哈桑的住所
Hassan's.
约翰的
John's.
这是美玲的地址
This is Mei Ling's address.
他们全都住在5英里半径内
They all lived within a five mile radius.
到这儿最近的医院是哪个?
What's the nearest hospital to here?
-我们在哪?-在这
-Where are we?-Right here.
科尼利厄斯大街,这里
St. Cornelius, right there.
科尼利厄斯大街..干得好!
St. Cornelius, good job!
美玲的家,452号
Mei Ling Hom. Number 452.
你说的这个人是谁?
Who'd you say she was?
我什么都没说
I didn't.
-你在这里等-不
-You wait out here.-No.
这是个太平间里面,艾米
This is a morgue, Amy.
我的照片也在文件里面
Now, my picture was in that file too.
你们进不进来?你们不能让人看见!
Are you coming or what? You can't be seen out here!
昨天真是疯狂的一天
It was like a fire sale yesterday.
每2个小时尸体运来一次
Bunch of bodies, coming in every other hour.
在斯凯尔特河边发现的..
She was found floating in the Scheldt.
酒精浓度:比正常高5倍
Blood alcohol level: five times the limit.
没有家庭,她住在法国
No next of kin. Still living in France.
法国?
France?
没有记录,一个非法移民
She was undocumented resident. An illegal immigrant.
你有10分钟
You have 10 minutes.
上帝!
Jesus!
潜在伤害
Latent injuries.
电击死亡,溺水,地铁内心脏病发作
Electrocution, drowning, heart attack on the metro.
-这些人是谁?-我的同事
-Who are these people?-My coworkers.
没有记录
Illegal immigrants.
要是我们回家也会遇上这种事,是吗?
If we'd have gone home would this have happened to us?
沃尔特失踪了
Walter's not here.
喂,需要帮忙吗?
Hello, can I help you?
你见过这些人吗?
Have you seen these people?
你还好吗?
You okay?
我还好
I'm fine.
我们走,艾米
Let's go, Amy.
你还好吗?
You okay?
让我来帮你背背包
Let me take your bag.
艾米,过来,告诉我一些事情
Amy, come here, talk to me.
别跟着我!
Get off me!
你可以徒手杀人
You can kill a man with your bare hands.
你可以穿越拥挤的火车站,不被警察盯上,即使你
You can move through a crowded station without the cops even knowing you're there.
-你会俄语!-克罗地亚语
-You can speak like, Russian!-Croatian.
不,你看看照片
No, you can look at a bunch of photos,
就会知道在哪找到尸体
and instinctively know where you'll find the bodies.
-谁的父亲会这样做?-我会解释的
-What father can do those things?-Let me explain.
不,解释这个:
No, explain this:
为什么你公司的同事全都没记录?
You've been working for a company that's only been employing immigrants,
全都死了?
who are now dead!
艾米
Amy..
-我为什么在这里?-艾米!
-Why did I even come here?-Amy!
为什么我必须离开祖父
Why did I even have to leave grandpa.
你告诉我让我相信你!我甚至不知道你是谁!
You told me to trust you! I don't even know who you are!
沃尔特!
Walter!
趴下!
Down!
快!
Come on!
爸爸!
Dad!
我带你出去
I'll get you out of here.
快点!
Come on!
-让我看看-小心!
-Let me see.-Be careful!
爸爸,你在流血
Dad, you've got a..
只是擦伤而已,你会没事的
It's just a flesh wound, you'll be okay.
拿着
Here.
去窗户那儿.去窗户那儿!
Go to the window. Go to the window!
开门!警察!
Open! Police!
快开门!
Open the door!
上车
Get in.
来,给你这个.紧紧压住你的手臂
Here, take this. Keep it pressed on your arm.
你会没事的
You'll be all right.
会有点刺痛,明白吗?
This is gonna sting a bit, okay?
抓住我的手
Hold my hand.
手臂放这儿
Put your arm up here.
你想知道我怎么发现尸体的?是吗?
You wanna know how I found the bodies? Is that it?
弗洛伊德的柜子是个保险柜
Floyd's locker was a safe drop.
那文件就是一个目标的列表
That file was a target hit list.
弗洛伊德是个职业杀手
And Floyd was a professional assassin.
遵循某种政府训练标准
Following some sort of government training protocol.
还可以吧?不会太紧吗?
Is that alright? Not too tight?
关于我,妈妈怎么告诉你的?
What did mom tell you about me?
你为国务院处理海外政治事务
That you were in Overseas Political Affairs for The State Department.
你母亲..
Your mother..
我过去在中情局工作
I was working for the CIA.
泛非洲议会的公报,安娜
The communiques on the Pan-African Council, Anna.
太好了,正是我需要的
Great, exactly what I needed.
这是每日简讯
It's for the daily brief.
弗洛伊德・莱米,前地方雇员,在路边被杀
Floyd Remi, former local operative, killed on a roadside.
布鲁塞尔郊外
Outside Brussels.
沃尔特・斯迈特,另一个前雇员
Walter Smet, another former asset.
几小时前,在安特卫普的一家医院被杀
Killed in a hospital in Antwerp only a couple of hours ago.
本・洛根,你的一名雇员,安娜
Ben Logan, one of your operatives, Anna.
我们认为可能是他杀死了他们
We think he may have killed them both.
-本在6个月前被除名了-除名?
-Ben was decommissioned six months ago.-Decommissioned?
-为什么?-他开窍了
-Why?-He grown a conscience.
不再服从命令
Stopped following orders.
监管委员会想杀一儆百
The Oversight Committee decided to make an example of him.
-我做了一个报告-他被驱逐出境了?
-I put his report on your desk when it happened.-Why wasn't he brought home?
他想回家
He wanted to go home.
但为了惩罚他,委员会拒绝他入境
But the Committee punished him, by making sure he'd never be able to.
永远不能回美国
He can't ever return to the U.S.
他试图联系过你吗?
Has he tried to contact you?
自从我们跟他切断关系后我就没跟本练联系过
I haven't spoken to Ben since we cut him loose.
发生什么事情了?
What's going on?
这是我们在布鲁塞尔的秘密安全屋
This is our black vault in Brussels.
我们保管着高度敏感的记录
We were using it as a repository for sensitive documentation.
两天前晚上的破门盗窃,有人闯入了
It was burgled two nights ago, by somebody who could break
我们最高防护的安全系统
our most advanced security systems.
这个圆筒装着高度机密的文件
That canister contained top-secret documents
美国司法部和..
we were collecting on behalf of The Department Of Justice
比利时的
in conjunction with the Belgian secret service.
有关什么?
Collecting evidence for what?
一个针对哈尔盖特集团在比利时的
It relates to a class action for negligence in Belgium
过失的集体诉讼
against The Halgate Group.
6个月前,他们的一艘商船沉没了
One of their merchant ships sank six months ago.
遇难者家属寻求赔偿
The families of the crewmen want compensation.
哈尔盖特集团愿意支付赔偿
Halgate is willing to settle,
但其中一个家庭拒绝妥协
but one family's holding out and putting together their case.
那个家庭的律师
The investigators for the family's lawyers
发现了一些诉讼案件背后的事情
discovered something bigger than a class action,
在货单中
something in the ship's manifest.
哈尔盖特与之有关联?
Incriminating Halgate?
从白宫发布的直接命令,这是最高度机密调查
On direct orders from the White House, this is a top level classified investigation.
你发现了什么?
What did you find?
确切的证据
A smoking gun.
有关哈尔盖特集团非法出口武器
That The Halgate Group was shipping illegal arms
为自己的利益引发政变
to destabilize countries for their own economic gain.
很自然,白宫认为颠覆他国政权是我们的工作
Naturally, the White House thinks it is our job to destabilize countries.
有人偷走了你的证据
Someone stole your smoking gun.
有人偷偷进入中情局总部
Someone breached into the CIA.
哈尔盖特是一个犯罪集团
Halgate is a criminal.
没有这个证据,针对哈尔盖特这个集团的调查就必须秘密进行
Without that evidence, the investigation against The Halgate Group will collapse.
涉及的利益实在太大
Stakes are too high.
我们只能继续调查那个洛根,一个高级保安系统专家
The only thing we have to go on is that Logan, a top security expert,
他当时在比利时
was in Belgium at the time of the break-in.
你能找到他吗?
Can you find him?
据说你和他有些私人关系
It's no secret you knew him intimately.
我懂了
I'll get on it.
德里克?
Derek?
你说过那事情不会发生的
You said this wouldn't happen.
什么不会发生?
What wouldn't happen?
你说过不会有人丧命的
You said no one was gonna die.
你错了!
This was all wrong!
-你是什么意思?-他们全都死了!
-And that means what?-It means they're all dead.
公司的全部雇员
The company, all the employees.
他们也想杀了我.你说只会给解雇通知书的!
And they're gonna kill me too. You said this would end in pink slips.
这不是解雇通知书!
This wasn't pink slips!
没我的允许不可能有任何擅自行动!
Nothing was supposed to go down without my approval!
他们把你剔除了
They cut you out of the equation.
谁给的命令?
Who gave the order?
布雷默
Braymer.
洛根在哪?
Where is Logan?
德里克,回答问题!
Derek, speak to me!
德里克!
Derek!
那个圆筒在你那里?
Did you secure the cargo?
对,在我这儿.但是现在,这件事要以我的方式来解决
Yeah, I have it. But now, this is gonna play out on my terms.
告诉布鲁塞尔领事馆,我会去当地召集人马
Tell the consulate in Brussels I'm coming in and raise a local team.
马上!
Now!
你妈妈和我想保护你
Your mom and I were trying to protect you.
是啊,远离真相
Yeah, from the truth.
爷爷知道吗?
Did grandpa know?
是的,他一直知道
Yeah, he always knew.
你在中情局是干什么的?
What exactly did you do for the CIA?
我帮助人们脱离..
I got people in and out of..
困境
difficult situations.
对不起,我们骗了你
I'm sorry we lied to you.
这张照片是你母亲拍的
Your mother took that photo.
对,她告诉过我
Yeah, she told me.
她知道我所不了解的事情
She could see things I never could.
我也想她
I miss her too.
-你为什么退出?-想成为一个真正的父亲
-Why'd you quit your job?-To be a father.
但我没有成功,对吗?
I'm not doing too good of a job of it, am I?
-我不确定-哦,真的?
-I wouldn't know.-Oh, really?
-我们不能回家,对吗?-对
-We can't go back home, can we?-No.
如果我们回家..
We go back home..
这些人找到我们两次,他们会再次找到我们
These people found us twice, they'll find us again.
这些人是谁?
Who are these people?
我不确定,我想我被利用了
I'm not sure. I think I was being used.
我只知道,这些设备过去都存在
All I know, those products were real.
如果不是哈尔盖特集团制造的,那就是另一个公司
And if Halgate wasn't making them, then somebody else was.
有人想让他们让步
Somebody wanted them compromised.
看这
Look at this.
这就是专利号码
That's a patent number.
它就刻在设备上面,我们必须搞清楚
It's etched into some of the products. We have to find out what's that all about.
那里就是我的办公室
Then there's my place of work.
这些地址,是线索
Addresses have owners, clues.
但我们目前必须先找到睡觉的地方
All we gotta do is figure out where we're to stay tonight.
可以给我些零钱吗?
Can I have some change?
纳比尔说他会帮忙的
Nabil said he'd help.
嗯?
Yes?
走吧
Come on.
卡里姆,这是我爸爸
Karim, this is my dad.
爸爸,这是纳比尔的哥哥,卡里姆
Dad, this is Nabil's brother, Karim.
你好,卡里姆
Hello, Karim.
很荣幸
It's a pleasure.
纳比尔说你会帮忙
Nabil said you'd help.
我说我愿意考虑
I said I'd think about it.
你在布鲁塞尔有藏身之处吗?
You found us a place in Brussels?
-我不会帮助罪犯-很好,因为我们不是罪犯
-I don't help criminals.-That's good, 'cause we're not criminals.
-可你们在逃亡-环境的牺牲品
-Yet you're fugitives.-Victims of circumstance.
2000欧元
2,000 euros.
付现金,预付一半,两个晚上
Cash. Half now, for two nights.
给我钱
Gimme the money.
纳比尔说你姐姐拿走了所有的钱,而你债台高筑
Nabil said your sister keeps all the money and you're up your ass in debt.
纳比尔太多话了
Nabil's got a big mouth.
你也应该改变自己
I suggest you change too.
快,我们走
Come on, let's go.
我女儿是你朋友,或者还有别的什么事情?
My daughter is just a friend or you want to tell me something?
不是,那是..
No, it's..
-嘿,你和他说什么?-去问他
-Hey, no fair, what'd you say?-Go ask him.
阿卜杜尔会给你们找个地方
Abdul will make sure you get a place.
看来,你可能比我更需要钱
And it seems to me, you probably need this more than I.
我们不会唯利是图
We are not all mercenaries.
他们是谁?
Who are they?
和你一样的流浪汉
You're not the only one on the run.
祝你好运
Good luck.
布鲁塞尔 比利时
好了,你们可以留下
It's okay, you can stay
两个晚上,在孩子的房间.行吗?
for two days in kids' rooms. Alright?
谢谢
Thank you.
在她生病期间
When she was sick,
她只提到你
you're all she talked about.
我想..
I think..
她仍爱你
I think she still loved you.
对不起,这么晚吵到你了
Sorry to get you guys up at this hour.
中情局安全机构 布鲁塞尔 比利时
我们在他公寓找到的
Everything we found in his apartment.
喂?
Hello?
你发现了什么?
What have you found?
他是被逐出境的前雇员,和他女儿生活在安特卫普
He was an expatriate living in Antwerp with his daughter.
记录显示,他两个月前来到这里,有商务签证
Records show, he moved here two months ago on a business visa.
别担心,我会找到他
Don't worry. I'll find him.
我觉得真的没有必要追究
My feeling is there's really no need to press
船上怎么会有破洞
for an excavation of the boat.
运输建筑材料常见的危险之一
Self-combustion is a common risk when you ship
就是自我燃烧
construction materials.
我相信我们会找到为这一悲剧事件补偿你们的方式
I'm sure we can find a way to compensate you for this tragic event.
不是钱的问题,布雷默先生
This is not about money, Mr.Braymer.
我想见哈尔盖特先生
I want Mr.Halgate
到这来,看着我的眼睛
to appear here personally and look me in the eye.
我要他对我儿子的死亡正式道歉
And I want him to apologize for my son's death.
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
你认为呢?
Where do you think?
你告诉我中情局那里有你想要的东西
You told me the CIA had something you wanted.
我已经有了
I arranged to get it.
-你为什么杀了这些人?-我们见个面
-Why did you murder these people?-Let's meet.
1个小时内..
One hour.
你终结了秘密行动
You dismantled the covert operation
我为你执行的行动
I was running for you.
你利用我的特工去杀人
You used my agents to kill.
你让洛根变成一个逃犯!你他妈究竟干嘛?
You've made Logan the subject of a manhunt! What the hell got into you?
他快要发现公司是假的了
He was about to find out the company was a fake.
是上面的决定
It was an executive decision.
洛根已经验证了专利
Logan was looking into the patents.
问起谁负责安保系统
Asking questions about who owned the security systems.
-你为什么让他参与?-因为你想要尽快完成!
-What possessed you to get him involved?-Because you wanted something done quick!
而他是最好的人选
And he's the best there is.
告诉我你还有证据吗?
Tell me you at least have the evidence.
你知道圆筒里是什么?
You know what was in the container?
-它在你手里?-我们正在努力
-Do you have it?-We're working on it.
圆筒在科勒手上,但我们找不到他,他不接电话
Kohler has the container but we can't find him, he's not answering his phone, he's..
他失踪了
He's gone.
你找不到科勒
You don't have Kohler.
你没有证据
You don't have the evidence.
-如果洛根知道真相..-他只是一个工程师
-If Logan finds out what we got him involved in..-He's just an engineer.
中情局黑色行动组的,你个白痴!我们没有单纯的工程师
CIA Black Ops, you idiot. We don't make engineers.
我们的头儿怀疑你对洛根的感情
Our employer wasn't sure your personal feelings for Logan
是否不会削弱你的判断力
wouldn't cloud your judgment in making the tough calls.
如果哈尔盖特完蛋,我也完蛋
If Halgate goes down, I go down.
如果洛根知道真相,不管你做多强的安全防范
No matter how much security you surround yourself with if Logan finds out,
你会找上你的.我能摆平这事!
he'll get to you. I can fix this!
找到科勒,把证据带回来
Find Kohler, bring in the evidence.
我们会给你他最新的所在地点
We'll get you his last known location.
那么本呢?
What about Ben?
我们叫一个专家来处理
We've got that covered. We brought in an expert.
-读出数字-好
-Give me the number.-Okay.
等一下,等一下
Hold on, hold on.
美国专利和商标局
-好了,给我专利号码-好的
-Alright. Give me the patent number now.-Okay.
XDN..
X-D-N
3-6-7.
美玲说对了
Mei Ling was right.
这个专利不属于哈尔盖特集团,而是属于纽约的"全方位安全"保安集团
Halgate doesn't own the patent. Belongs to Total Security in New York.
抄下来:785506..
Write that down: 785506.
中央情报局,需要帮忙吗?
Central Intelligence Agency, may I help you?
听好了
Alright, are you ready for this?
你的办公室地址,是由哈尔盖特安全公司短期租借的
Your office address, the address for Halgate Security System was short-leased,
六个月前,由马库斯・沃尔夫投资公司租用
six months ago to a company called Markus Wolf Investments.
这家公司还有其他的本地地址
That company also has another local registered address
由布鲁塞尔本地的房产经纪人承租
by the same realtor, right here in Brussels.
-那个房产经纪人告诉你的?-对,我知道,他们想快点租出去
-The realtor just told you this?-Yeah, I know, they're dying to lease it.
我们必须加把劲了,因为周末了,经纪人很忙的
We gotta hurry, because it's Saturday and the realtor gets busy.
我们半个小时后见面
I put this at viewing in 30 minutes.
你以为自己是谁,侦探福尔摩斯?
Who you think you are, Sherlock Holmes?
我去拿我的包包
I'm gonna go get my bag.
你的上一个租客,你见过他吗?
What about the previous occupant, you ever meet him?
沃尔夫先生,他有一家投资公司
Mr.Wolf, he's running an investment company.
让我们单独待会,好吗?
Would you mind giving us a minute?
当然
Sure.
-我在车上等-谢谢
-I'll be in the car.-Thank you.
-看着她了吗?-是的
-Got an eye on her?-Yeah.
-马库斯・沃尔夫是谁?-冷战时期东德间谍头目
-Who is Markus Wolf?-He's an East German cold-war spy master.
开玩笑
Somebody's idea of a joke.
-等等,他没死?-不,他应该死了差不多5年了
-Wait, so he's not even alive?-No, he's been dead 5 years or so.
看来我任职于某家专卖公司
Looks like I was working for some kind of proprietary.
什么专卖公司?
What's a proprietary?
一个空壳公司,什么都不制造
It's a shell company, created to do one thing,
而事实上,他们在做完全不同的事情
when in reality, it's doing something completely different.
等等,为什么中情局给一个空壳公司申请专利?
So wait, why would the CIA file patents for a shell company?
艾米,等会儿再问,好吗?
Amy, quit with the questions for a minute, okay?
线路还没有中断
Disconnection hasn't gone through yet.
查到了!
Bingo!
我在线上查了马库斯・沃尔夫投资公司
I pulled up caller records on Markus Wolf Investments.
公司昨天已被关闭
Now, that office was closed yesterday,
但1小时前有一个电话从那儿打出
but there was a call made from there about an hour ago.
本..
Ben.
我们得走了
We have to move.
马库斯・沃尔夫,619套房
Markus Wolf, suite 619.
注意观察,通过镜子
Keep your eyes open. Through the mirrors.
-记住..-角落是安全的
-Remember..-Corners are safe.
别耍小聪明
Don't be a smart ass.
你是我的耳目,明白吗?
You're my eyes and ears, okay?
马库斯・沃尔夫是你的化名?
Markus Wolf is your alias, huh?
真有趣.下一次用什么,玛塔・哈里?
That's cute. What's next, Mata Hari?
你犯大错了!
You're making a big mistake!
根本没有什么产品研发队伍,是吗,德里克?
There was no product development team, was there, Derek?
也没有什么哈尔盖特安保系统!
There was no Halgate security systems!
你让我们闯入中情局!
You got us hack into CIA!
走吧
Come on.
为什么?
Why?
为了什么?
For what?
你为谁工作?
Who are you working for?
趁还有时间,你快点离开,本!
Get outta here while you still can, Ben.
去哪儿,你个狗娘养的!
Go where, you son of a bitch!
你最好快点说,伙计
You gotta start talking, pal.
你让我女儿处在危险中,我想知道原因!
You put my daughter's life in danger. I want answers!
她说只是简单行动
She said it was a simple operation.
-她是谁?-她告诉他们去雇用你
-Who's she?-She told them to hire you.
她说没有你,我们别指望发现那个文档
She said we never recover the documents without you.
什么文档?
Recover what documents?
-什么文档?-爸爸!
-Recover what documents?-Dad!
沙发上圆筒里面那个
In the canister on the couch.
在外面等,出去!
Wait outside. Go on!
去外面等,快!
Wait outside, go on!
我也有孩子
I got a family, too.
这是为了我的退休金
This was gonna be my pension.
-如果我死了,他们会照看我的家人-谁?
-If I die, they'll look after my family.-Who will look after your family?
特工机构
The Agency.
-你在中情局?-打死我!
-You were CIA?-Shoot me!
-爸!-打死我!
-Dad!-Shoot me!
来
Come here.
搜查房间
Get the room searched.
本!
Ben!
退后!
Go back!
快!过去!
Go! Over here!
上去!快,跳过去!
Get up! Come on, get over!
别开枪!
Stand down!
我说了,别开枪!他是我们的一分子!
I said, stand down! He's one of us, for Christ sakes!
本?
Ben?
不管怎样,我们都会找到解决办法的
Whatever is going on, we can figure it out.
我们能保护你
We can protect you.
你们两个
Both of you.
本?
Ben?
退后!
Back off!
放下武器!
Put them down!
靠后站
Stand back.
踢远点!
Kick them away!
你让我牵扯进了什么,安娜?
What have you got me involved with, Anna?
你完全弄错了
You've got this all wrong.
-你要相信我-爸爸,上来!
-You gotta trust me.-Dad, get in!
退后!
Get back!
他们会找到你
They'll find you.
他们会杀了你,他们会杀了她!
They'll kill you. They'll kill her!
-我能帮忙让你回家-爸爸,上车!
-I can help you go home.-Dad, get in the car!
-不,请听我说..-为什么?
-No, listen to me, please!-Why?
六个月前当我被组织除名的的时候,你袖手旁观
You stood by six months ago and watched the Committee burn me.
袖手旁观?你是杀手小组的成员!你违抗命令!
Stood by? You were part if a kill squad! You questioned your orders!
没有我,他们早就杀了你
I was the one who stopped them from killing you.
爸爸,上车!
Dad, get in the car!
把袋子给我,本
Give me the bag, Ben.
你很棒,安娜
You're good, Anna.
非常有天赋
You're very good.
本!
Ben!
开始吧!
Go!
-她是谁?-你教你开车的?
-Who is she?-Who taught you to drive?
不,她是谁?
No, who is she?
我以前的一个同事
Just someone I used to work with.
中情局
CIA.
-你在干嘛?-别骗我,我不是白痴,我见过你
-What are you doing?-Don't lie to me, I'm not an idiot, I saw you.
慢点,艾米
Slow down, Amy.
什么是杀手小组?什么是杀手小组的?
What's a kill squad? What's a kill squad?
慢点,艾米!
Slow down, Amy!
艾米,刹车!
Amy, brakes!
我杀人
I kill people.
杀手小组就是干这个的,杀人
That's what a kill squad is all about, killing people.
肮脏的工作
The dirty work.
必须有个了了结了
The things that have to be done.
没人想做的事
The things nobody wants to do.
我去做
I did these things.
我不想我女儿知道
I never wanted my daughter to find out.
你没回来找我
You didn't come back for me.
我找过!
I did!
你来找我,是因为你无路可走了
You've came to me, because you had nowhere else to go.
我有朋友
I had friends.
我有我的生活,爸爸!
I had a life, dad!
你带我
You brought me
去异国他乡
to a foreign country,
骗我到这儿来
lied, to get me here.
你所有的话都是骗我的
You lied to me about everything.
你就不能别管我?
Why couldn't you just leave me alone?
艾米!
Amy!
我需要打个电话
I need a telephone.
电话
A telephone.
喂?
Hello?
祖父?
Grandpa?
艾米,哦,我的天,你怎么样?
Amy, oh, my God, are you okay?
我曾试着给你电话,你在哪儿?
I've been trying to call you. Where are you?
祖父,我想回家
Grandpa, I wanna come home.
你的声音挺吓人的,都还好吧?
You sound terrible. Is everything alright?
艾米?喂..?
Amy? Hello?
嘿,你!我在跟你说!
Hey, you! I'm talking to you!
他们在我5岁外甥女面前,杀了我哥哥!
They killed my brother in front of my five year old niece!
他们要的是你!他们是谁?
They were looking for you! I want their names!
我要知道他们是谁!我要他们死!
I want to know who they are! I want them dead!
我也一样
So do I.
他们绑架了艾米
They took Amy.
上车!
Get in the car!
货物清单
"SAX-135"固态
Altheon X-135 solid state.
"XTA-20"波兰进行曲
"Xyston TA-20" Polemarch.
什么是波兰进行曲?
What's a "Polemarch"?
波兰进行曲..
Polemarch.
这是一个雷达追踪系统
It's a radar tracking system.
防御系统的一部分
It's parts inside IAT drone defense system.
货船运的是美国武器
That cargo ship was carrying U.S. made weapons.
给莫桑比克的
For Mozambique.
为了确保业务安全..
..necessary conditions to secure business..
锂
Lithium.
-什么是锂?-下一代工业技术
-What's a Lithium?-Next generation technology.
原子能
Nuclear power.
..手机,电动汽车,那一类的东西
Mobile telecommunications, electric cars, that kind of thing.
哈尔盖特集团
Halgate Group.
安娜
Anna.
艾米呢?
What about Amy?
我们应该去找她
I thought we were trying to find her.
"詹姆斯・哈尔盖特三世"
"James Halgate III."
我们找到它了
We just did.
喂?
Hello?
你知道我拿到了什么?
You know what I have?
我正在听
I'm listening.
巴黎北站,4号站台,1个小时后见
Gare du Nord, Platform 4, one hour.
喂?
Hello?
有辆列车,5号站台
There's a train, Platform 5.
上去
Get on it.
第一节车厢
Front carriage.
去!那里!
Go! Over there!
离开列车,快
Get off the train, now.
有辆火车向8号站台开来
There's a train pulling into Platform 8.
快
Hurry.
最后一节车厢
Rear compartment.
那才是我认识的安娜
That's the Anna I know.
我知道你向哈尔盖特集团出售服务
I see you've been selling your services to The Halgate Group.
哈尔盖特在中情局内部派卧底多久了?
How long has Halgate been reaching into the CIA?
你跟他上床有多久了,安娜?
How long have you been in bed with him, Anna?
从索马里开始的?
All the way back to Somalia?
不
No.
我一直记得你刚来到索马里的时候
I'll never forget the first day you showed up in Somalia.
准备要一鸣惊人
Ready to set the world on fire.
我们有理想
We stood for something.
我们相信我们能改变世界
We believed we could change the world.
现在你怎么样了,安娜?
What do you believe in now, Anna?
我想你应该听我说
I believe you should have listened to me.
我告诉过你
I told you,
这些人不达目的,誓不罢休
these people will sop at nothing to get what they want.
你怎么变成你所憎恨的那些人了?
How did you become everything we fought against?
这只是生意,本
It's just business, Ben.
这关系到我女儿的生活!
It's my daughter's life!
把他们想要的给他们
Just give them what they want.
哦,是啊,是啊,那样我们就安全了?
Oh, yeah, yeah. And then we'll be safe, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
我帮不上忙
I can't.
我要你找到你老板,你真正的老板,把这个信息告诉他
I want you to go your boss, your real boss, with a message.
我知道他是谁
I know who he is.
我知道他会在哪
I know where he's gonna be.
如果他绑了我女儿,我要要回她
If he has her, I want her.
如果他伤害她
If he's harmed her,
他必死无疑
he's dead.
我只找到这个
It was the only one I could find.
有用吗?
Would it do?
哦,是的
Oh, yeah.
谢谢你,纳比尔,太好了
Thank you, Nabil. That's perfect.
詹姆斯・哈尔盖特三世今天到达比利时..
James Halgate III has arrived in the Belgium
法院希望尽早了结这一漫长的
courthouse today in an effort to settle the longstanding
针对他的公司的诉讼.该诉讼
class action suit against his company. The suit was put forth
是由那些遇难者家属提起的
by the bereaved families of those who lost loved ones,
哈尔盖特公司的船只,宁静号
when the ship owned by The Halgate Group, The Serenity,
沉没于比利时海岸
sank off the coast of Belgium.
一共有150人在此悲剧中遇难
150 lives were lost in this tragedy.
皮特斯小姐
Ms Pieters,
我向你表达衷心的哀悼
I am deeply sorry for your loss.
我希望你能接受我们的帮助
I hope you will accept our offer of support
在你需要的时刻
in your hour of need.
有一个我不知道的契约?
Is there a settlement I don't know about?
不,抱歉,我无可奉告
No, I'm sorry, I don't comment.
对不起,无可奉告,非常感谢
I'm sorry, no comment. Thank you very much.
我回头来找你
I'll catch you later.
找你的!
For you!
以后我会告诉你.非常感谢
I'll talk to you later. Thank you very much.
你老板一个人来
Your boss comes alone.
当我知道她安全的时候,你就会收到证据
When I know she's safe, you'll get your evidence.
我在听着
I'm listening.
拿着这手机,我会发简讯告诉你时间和地点
Keep this phone on you. I'll text you a time and a place.
等一下!
Hold it!
-我告诉你等等!-我必须跟他说话
-I told you to wait!-I need to speak to him.
-他在跟地区总裁开会-我才不管
-He's dealing with the regional president.-I don't give a shit.
他不和小角色讲话
He doesn't meet the help.
安娜!
Anna!
哈尔盖特先生?
Mr.Halgate?
-我不知道我们有预约-她要走了
-I didn't realize we had a one o'clock.-She was just leaving.
他要杀了你
He's going to kill you.
你一定就是善变的安娜・勃兰特
You must be the mercurial Anna Brandt.
-过奖!-你抓了那个女孩
-I'm honored!-You took the girl.
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
这么多麻烦就因为一个小事故!
So much trouble because of one little accident!
就为了一次沉船
Because one little ship sinks.
我4个小时后飞回芝加哥
I'm flying back to Chicago in exactly four hours.
我要在我离开前解决这件事
I need this fixed before I leave.
让我去交换,我了解本
Let me make the exchange. I know Ben.
看起来你很关心他的幸福,安娜
You seem very concerned about his welfare, Anna.
我为你放弃了我全部的事业
I've compromised my entire career for you.
为了那些幻想中的钱
For money that's in an account I can't touch
如果都安全
if this blows up.
在这情形下,我会做出适当的安排
I'll do whatever needs to be done to neutralize the situation.
你我的意见相同,安娜
You and I are cut from the same cloth, Anna.
我们知道如何达到我们的目标
We know what we want and how to get it.
我们能在需要的时候做出艰难的决定
We're capable of making the tough calls when required.
吉姆,你说我们可以自己做
Jim, you said we could do this ourselves.
是洛根
It's Logan.
司法部外面的纪念碑下
The monument by the Palace of Justice.
3点
At three.
-我去叫车-不需要
-I'll get the car.-There's no need.
我之所以来这个破地方
The only reason I came to this backwater,
是为了确保能带着我的证据离开
was to make sure I'm on the plane home with my evidence.
安娜会给我带来的
Anna will get it for me.
快跑,艾米!
Run, Amy!
快跑!
Run!
我现在叫车?
Shall I get the car now?
我告诉你必须一个人来
I thought I told you to come alone.
布雷默先生和我们的利益一致
Mr.Braymer is here to serve our mutual interests.
也许他能告诉我买下中情局要多少钱?
Maybe he can tell me how much it cost to buy the CIA?
毛重还是净重?
Are we talking gross or net?
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
你给我们要的,你会得到你想要的
You give us what we want, you'll get what you want.
你煽动发起了内战
You fan the flames of a civil war.
向各个部落出售武器
Selling weapons to tribal factions.
-为了什么?为了获取锂矿?-保护我们的利益
-For what? Access to lithium mines?-Protecting our interests.
在空闲时间里他们干什么,那是他们的事情
What these people did in their spare time, was their own business.
对,除非司法部准备调查你
Yeah, except The Justice Department was gonna figure you out.
所以你雇佣移民来做这个工作
So you hired a bunch of immigrants to do the work.
然后当他们越线了..
Then when they step out of line..
-洛根先生!-他们就得死!
-Mr.Logan!-People have died!
所以你就能掩盖你们的所作所为
So you could cover your tracks.
信任
Trust,
洛根先生
Mr.Logan,
是一种宝贵的资源
is a precious resource.
给我那些文档,本
Give me the documents, Ben.
不要忽略现实,像安娜那样
Don't lose sight of reality, like Anna did.
-安娜在哪?-我只能说她不是一个团队的
-Where is Anna?-Let's just say she wasn't a team player.
丢掉你心里的道德罗盘吧,本,它能对你有什么帮助?
Don't let your noble moral compass get in the way, Ben. Where has it gotten you?
你一无所有
You have nothing.
没有工作
No job.
没有钱
No money.
没有国家
No country.
-把我女儿给我-不
-Give me my daughter.-No.
得用你..
It has to be you,
换她
for her.
-我们有过协议-现在我们重新谈判
-We had a deal.-And now we're negotiating terms.
哦,我相信你能理解我们的处境
Oh, I'm sure you can understand our position.
你好吗?他们伤害你了吗?
You okay? Did they hurt you?
看看你
Look at you.
-拿这这个-怎么回事?
-Take this.-What's going on?
你会没事的
You're gonna be just fine.
我要你走得远远的
I want you to leave and get as far away as you can.
不
No.
我必须留下来
I have to stay here.
-不,你不能那么做,你..-我别无选择
-No, you can't do that, you..-I have no choice.
-这是我的使命-不,不是的!
-This is who I am.-No, it's not!
这就是我的用处
This is how I make a difference.
走!
Go.
不要遗憾
Don't have any second thoughts.
要不是你她不会获得自由
She'll never be free if you do.
我相信你忘了一些事情
I believe you've forgotten something.
你看起来不像中情局的人
You don't look like CIA.
你是英国人?军情六局的?
What are you, British? MI6?
克格勃?
KGB?
你的老板已经忘记了
Tell your boss he forgot a piece.
你不该就这么让那女孩走
You can't seriously let the girl go.
一星期.再找人"照顾"她祖父一个星期
A week. Send someone to take care of the grandfather too.
你到那儿就给我电话,好吗?
Call me when you get there, okay?
好的
Okay.
走
Go.
你好!谢谢
Hello! Thank you.
飞往纽约F714航班,最后一次提醒
Last call for FWA flight 714 to New York.
现在请剩下的所有旅客登机
All remaining passengers, please board now.
乘客马库斯・沃尔夫,请去柜台
Stand by, passenger Markus Wolf, please, come to the counter.